我怎么了
What happened to me?
前情提要
我很抱歉 我试图警告你的 我的血液进入你的身体里了
I'm sorry. I tried to warn you. My blood got into your system.
所以我现在也能变成浩克了
So I turn into a Hulk now too.
你是何方神圣
Who the hell are you?
-女浩克 -沃尔特斯小姐
- She-Hulk! She-Hulk! She-Hulk! - Ms Walters?
我们刚刚成立了一个 超能人类法务部
We just started a Superhuman Law Division,
我想请女浩克做部门负责人
and I want the She-Hulk to be the face of it.
无论分派给我的是什么案子 我都想尽快接手...
I can't wait to take on whatever case you assign me...
你的第一个案子是 埃米尔·布朗斯基假释案 也就是憎恶
Your first case is the parole of Emil Blonsky. Also known as Abomination.
珍妮佛·沃尔特斯
Jennifer Walters.
我已经有个必胜的策略了 百分之百保证胜诉
I've already got a winning strategy, and it is 100% in the bag.
也许你应该看看现在的新闻
You might wanna take a look at the news right now.
根据一段令人震惊的视频 我们可以看到憎恶
After shocking footage leaked showing the Abomination
参与了一场地下搏击俱乐部的比赛
participating in what appears to be an underground fight club,
不知他是通过何种手段越狱的
after having escaped from prison.
能不能解释一下 为什么之前你没提到
Do you wanna explain to me why you failed to mention
你不但越狱了 还被拍到了这些
that you not only escaped from prison, but you were also recorded doing so?
你可是当着我的面说 你永远不会变成憎恶了
You said to my face that you never turn into the Abomination anymore.
不 我说的是我选择不变身
No, I said I choose not to.
其实这是情有可原的
You know, these were extenuating circumstances.
你知道这种行为 不但构成了另一项犯罪
You understand that this constitutes another crime
还会彻底毁了你假释的机会吗
and totally destroys your chances at parole?
什么
What?
不会吧 因为我是被迫离开牢房的
Nah, 'cause I was forced to leave my cell,
但是我可是完全自愿回来的
but I returned of my own free will.
是谁强迫你神不知鬼不觉地 逃出戒备这么森严的监狱的
Who forced you to escape this insanely high-security prison undetected?
一位驾驭秘术的至上尊者 他的名字叫...
A Sorcerer Supreme of the Mystic Arts, and his name is...
王 就叫王
Wong. Just Wong.
而且他在网上也有点神出鬼没
And his Internet presence is a little chaotic.
一会是住在纽约的法师
He's either a sorcerer who lives in New York,
一会是住在尼泊尔的图书管理员
or a librarian who lives in Nepal.
你能联系上他吗
Can you get to him?
能啊 珍妮佛 你放心 我当然能联系上他
Yes, Jen. It's me. Of course I can get to him.
我想了个妙招 我给他发了张我和一摞书的靓照
I sent a thirst trap. It was a picture of me with a bunch of books.
好吧 希望他能回电话
Yeah, well, let's just hope he calls back.
如果布朗斯基说的是实话
If Blonsky's telling the truth,
那这家伙就是帮他越狱的人 估计会搞砸整个案子
this guy busted him out of his prison cell and probably ruined my entire case.
我知道你们迫不及待想看到王 我能理解
I know you can't wait to see Wong. I get it.
我只是希望你们别以为
I wanna make sure that you don't think
这部剧每周都有明星客串 并不是那样的
this is one of those cameo every week type of shows. It's not.
当然 布鲁斯不算
Well, except Bruce.
还有布朗斯基 还有王
And Blonsky. And Wong.
但是别忘了谁才是这部剧的主角
Just remember whose show this actually is.
《律师女浩克》
第一季第三集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
新闻在线 洛杉矶
来自古利库霍律所的律师 珍妮佛·沃尔特斯
Attorney Jennifer Walters of law firm GLK and H
被委任为埃米尔·布朗斯基 也就是“憎恶”的代理律师
has been tapped to represent Emil Blonsky, also known as the Abomination,
负责他即将到来的假释听证会
in his upcoming parole hearing.
这则消息引发了巨大的舆论争议
The news has stirred up much controversy.
自从珍妮佛·沃尔特斯
Ever since it's been revealed that
被爆出拥有一个名为“女浩克”的 超级英雄身份之后
Jennifer Walters has a superhero alter-ego called She-Hulk,
这位身形健美的绿色律师 持续遭到大众抨击
the statuesque green lawyer has been plagued by public backlash,
其中不乏许多质疑其能力的声音
with many questioning her qualifications.
全网热议女浩克
在过去的一小时里 “巨型绿色女人”这一标签
还有“大号绿皮女”等热搜词
已经蹿升为全球热搜
浩克不应该是纯爷们吗  怎么女的也能变成浩克了
They took the Hulk's manhood away, but then they gave it to a woman?
我不理解 为什么非得把超级英雄都变成女的
MAN 2: I don't get it. Why are you turning every superhero into a girl?
就因为搞了MeToo运动 男性超级英雄就都消失了
MAN 3: So we have a MeToo movement, and now all the male heroes are gone?
我对女性英雄没什么意见 我只是说能不能有点个性
I have no problem with female heroes. Just saying make your own.
我不知道你们 但是我也会砸
I don't know about y'all, but I'd smash.
对话杰斐逊·库普
We have Gideon Wilson, the prosecutor
我们即将连线的是吉迪恩·威尔逊
who put the Abomination away all those years ago. Gideon.
他就是多年前将憎恶送进监狱的检察官 吉迪恩
首先我要说的是 我很震惊
First, I would like to say, it is frankly appalling that
有人想把憎恶这样的怪物放出来...
anyone would work towards freeing a monster like the...
-你看这个胡说八道的节目了吗  -我才不在乎别人怎么说我
- Have you seen this insanity? - I don't care what anybody says about me.
在这个国家里 凡事都得有正当程序
There's something in this country called due process.
-埃米尔有权得到公平的听证 -你得做出回应
- Emil deserves a fair hearing. - You have to respond.
你得把主动权掌握在自己手里
You have to be in control of your own narrative.
我是珍妮佛·沃尔特斯
Jennifer Walters speaking.
好的 我这就过去
Yes, I will be right there.
霍利韦叫我过去
Holliway beckons.
别这样 这可是大案子
Come on. This case is huge.
人们想了解你生活的每个细节
People wanna know every single detail about your life.
你现在可是公众人物
You're a public figure now.
办公室的电话都被打爆了 全是想采访你的
The office has been flooded with calls and requests for interviews,
所以你应该有个回应
so you should do one.
大家关注我只是因为 我是埃米尔·布朗斯基的代理律师
People only care because I'm representing Emil Blonsky.
案子一结束 这些媒体就会作鸟兽散
Once that's over, this whole media circus will die down.
不 珍妮佛 就算你选择视而不见 他们也不会善罢甘休
No, Jen, this is not gonna go away just because you're ignoring it.
我在这些破事上浪费一分钟
Every minute I spend on this crap
我的工作时间就少一分钟
is one less minute I spend focusing on my job.
这也太不合理了吧 我真的非常不爽
This is absolutely ridiculous. I am incredibly upset.
什么办公室居然连瓶红牛都没有
What kind of office doesn't have any Red Bulls?
-丹尼斯 -不是吧 珍妮佛·沃尔特斯可不行
- Dennis. - No way... Not Jen Walters.
沃尔特斯小姐是超能人类法务部的领导
Ms. Walters is head of the Superhuman Law Division.
我们俩太多恩怨了 我可没法和她共事
We have too much history for me to be comfortable with her on the case.
我倒是想听听是个什么案子 虽然我是不会接的
I would love to know what this is about and not work on it.
-您是要找我吗  -对
- You wanted to see me? - Ah, yes.
这位马洛里·布克 也是超能人类法务部的
Mallory Book is also in the Superhuman Law Division.
好吧 也不行 她太完美了 那些尴尬的事我没法启齿
Yeah. No, I can't talk to a 10 about embarrassing man stuff.
她没准是我将来的未婚妻呢
She could be my next fiancée.
幸好没我的事
Happy to not be involved.
他是律师吗  看着还不错 我就选他了
Is he a lawyer? He looks cool. I'll take him.
好吧 我们的朋友 地方检察院的布科夫斯基先生
Well, our friend, Mr. Bukowski from the DA's office,
有个棘手的事需要帮助
needs help on a delicate matter.
他被前女友诈骗
He's been defrauded by an ex-girlfriend
想对她提起诉讼 然后把钱追回来
and wants to file a suit against her to get his money back.
对 我给她买了珠宝 出钱让她飞去巴厘岛拍写真
Yeah. I bought her jewelry, flew her to Bali for a photo-shoot,
还清了她那辆帕萨特的车贷 还给她订了...
paid off her Volkswagen Passat. Subscribed to...
为什么找超能人类法务部
But why the Superhuman Law Division?
他的女朋友是个会变身的光之精灵 来自新阿斯加德
The girlfriend in question is a shapeshifting Light Elf from New Asgard.
真厉害啊 丹尼斯
Wow, Dennis.
好吧 其实我还以为和我约会的是 梅根·西·斯塔莉安
Okay. Well, to be fair, I thought I was dating Megan Thee Stallion.
你说什么
I'm sorry. What?
不好意思 你以为你约会的是 梅根·西·斯塔莉安
Sorry. You thought you were dating Megan Thee Stallion?
多项格莱美奖得主 超级巨星梅根·西·斯塔莉安
Multiple Grammy award-winner megastar Megan Thee Stallion?
你是听不明白什么叫“变身”吗
What part of "shapeshifter" did you not get?
-你觉得她可能开帕萨特吗  -这就是我不想找沃尔特斯的原因
- You thought she drove a Passat? - This is why I don't want Walters.
真不好意思
I'm so sorry.
沃尔特斯小姐 我收到你的消息了
Ms. Walters, I received your message.
这位是王先生 出场很酷 来得正是时候
Uh, Mr. Wong. Great entrance. Perfect timing.
-我得去办正事了 -忙你的去吧
- I really need to take this. - You may go.
谢谢 巴戈 祝你好运
Thank you. Uh, Pug, good luck.
丹尼斯...
Dennis...
不好意思
Sorry.
布朗斯基说的都是事实
Everything Mr. Blonsky told you is factual.
是我把他从监狱里弄出去的 并非他自己有意而为之
I extracted him from the prison against his own wishes,
因为在成为至上尊者的训练中
because I required a worthy opponent
我需要一个旗鼓相当的对手
as part of my training to become Sorcerer Supreme.
而作为至上尊者 我希望 不要因为我的举动而给他带来惩罚
And as Sorcerer Supreme, I insist that he not be punished for my actions.
再说一遍 不是我要惩罚他
Again, I am not the one who will be punishing him.
看过视频后 假释委员会不可能把他放出去
The parole board will not release him after seeing this video.
我知道你在想什么 沃尔特斯小姐 我再也不会消除大家的记忆了
I know what you're thinking, Ms. Walters, and I'm not erasing everyone's memories.
绝不再干了
Not again.
我可没这么想 这非常违背职业道德
That is not what I was thinking. That is highly unethical.
对 而且会非常混乱 相信我
Yeah, it's also very messy, believe me.
-好吧 -把他们送去镜像次元空间吧
- Okay. - We'll send him to the Mirror Dimension.
-虽然我不懂那是什么 但是不行 -那暗影次元空间呢
- Don't know what that is, but no. - Shadow Dimension?
你可以做的是出席听证会 把一切解释清楚
What you can do to help is show up at the hearing and explain everything.
好吧 那秘术就留作备用方案
Very well. We'll reserve sorcery for strategy B.
没什么可保密的
Don't tap your nose.
那么布科夫斯基先生 现金加礼物
So, Mr. Bukowski, how much money in cash and gifts
你一共为冒牌的梅根·西·斯塔莉安 花了多少钱
did you spend on the Megan Thee Stallion imposter?
天啊
Oh, man.
要不然我说个数字 你告诉我是多了还是少了 可以吗
How about I just say a number, and you tell me higher or lower, okay?
参考你给她买的中型轿车 大概5万
Considering that you bought her a mid-sized sedan, how about $50,000?
10万
100?
- 20万  - 20万 我又不傻
- 200? - $200,000? I am not a fool.
-没有 差不多17万5吧 - 17万5000美金
- No, it was more like 175. - 100... $175,000?
在很多地方够买一栋房子了 布科夫斯基先生
That's a house in parts of the country, Mr. Bukowski.
没错 是啊
Yeah, right.
所以你能帮我吗
So, are you gonna help me or not?
我会着手梳理案情 并跟你保持联系 布科夫斯基先生
I'm gonna start building your case, and I will be in touch, Mr. Bukowski.
好吧
All right.
Okay.
冒牌梅根·西·斯塔莉安 在商场大打出手
我根本就不是梅根·西·斯塔莉安
I'm not really Megan Thee Stallion.
打扰了 哥们 你好啊
What's up, bro? How's it hanging, man?
我改主意了 我不起诉了
I got a change of heart. I'm gonna drop the case.
等等 怎么回事 你刚刚还...
Wait. What? Just now? You just...
其实你知道吗  在内心深处我很清楚
The truth is, I think somewhere deep inside, I knew. You know?
我送她那些东西是因为我愿意
I gave those things 'cause I wanted to.
我只是因为闹得人尽皆知 所以觉得有点丢脸
I was just embarrassed to get found out in such a public way.
不过早晚有一天 你得为自己的行为负责
But at some point in time, you gotta take personal responsibility.
-我不得不说 这让我有点意外 -说到底不就是点钱嘛
- I have to say, this is unexpected. - Well, it's just money after all.
而我有...我有件事要说
And now, I have a... I got a story to tell.
不好意思 稍等...您好
- I'm sorry, Mr... This is Pug.
哥们 有人把我的赛博卡车拖走了
Hey, man. I think somebody towed my Cybertruck.
他们说这是残障人士车位 我发誓这是赛博卡车专用车位
They're saying it was a handicapped spot. I swear it was a Cybertruck spot.
喂 你在听吗
Hello? You there?
我开赛博卡车把你吓着了吧
Your jaw's on the floor because I drive a Cybertruck.
保安
Security!
我就喜欢调戏办公室的女同事们 超级刺激 宝贝
I love harassing women in the workplace. It's my kick, baby.
-你不能这样 -给你个警告
- Not cool. - Let that be a warning.
我才没有
I don't.
你们了解我
You guys know me.
我们正在戒备极为森严的监狱外 为您现场直播
We're coming to you live from outside the ultra-high security prison
稍后那位名为“憎恶”的犯人 将与假释委员会见面
where the man known as the Abomination will appear before a parole board.
其有望获批的假释申请 已经引起公愤...
There is much public furor over the possible release of...
等等 那是她吗  女浩克 我们能聊几句吗
Wait. Is that her? She-Hulk, can we get a word?
复仇者联盟拒绝你加入是真的吗
Is it true you were rejected by the Avengers?
那就是珍妮佛·沃尔特斯 也就是女浩克
That was Jennifer Walters, also known as She-Hulk,
有传闻说 她已经被复仇者联盟拒之门外
rumored to have been rejected by the Avengers.
-你准备好了吗  -当然
- Hey. Are you ready for this? - Yeah.
她们就是你的笔友
Uh, are those your soulmates?
-对啊 -好的
- Ah, yeah. - Okay.
王来了吗
Is Wong about?
还没有 我无法理解 一个能随意传送的人居然会迟到
No. I don't understand how a guy with zero commute time is late.
我们今日将在此决定 埃米尔·布朗斯基
We are here today to determine whether Emil Blonsky is
在服完最低刑期之后 是否有资格回归社会
suitable for return to society after having served his minimum sentence.
最近有证据表明他存在越狱行为
In light of recent evidence of a prison escape,
相信各位都有自己的判断 所以我们尽量速战速决
I think we all know how this is gonna go. So, let's keep this brief.
作为布朗斯基先生的代理律师 我想就越狱行为作如下澄清
As Mr. Blonsky's counsel, I would love to address the alleged prison escape.
我们有一位证人
We do have a witness
能够洗清布朗斯基先生 所有不当行为的罪名
who is able to clear Mr. Blonsky of any wrongdoing on his part.
那就从他开始吧
Then we'll start with that then.
好吧 对 这位证人已经准备好
Well, yes, the witness is prepared to give a statement
在布朗斯基先生陈述后发言
after Mr. Blonsky gives his.
此人越狱证据确凿
Are we really entertaining the idea of releasing
我们真的有必要考虑假释他吗
someone who's been documented escaping from prison?
稍等 布朗斯基先生 你认为自己已经改过自新了吗
Now hold on. Mr. Blonsky, do you feel you have been rehabilitated?
首先我要说 我现在无比懊悔
Let's start by saying that I feel great remorse,
对那些我伤害过的人感到无比羞愧
great shame to those that I've harmed.
接下来回答您的问题 是的 我认为我已经改过自新了
So, to answer your question, yes, I feel I have been rehabilitated.
被监禁的每一天 我无时无刻不在想着怎么能赎罪
I've spent every day of my incarceration focused solely on redemption.
我已经洗心革面了
I have changed.
无论是情感层面 身体层面 玄学层面 精神层面
Emotionally, physically, metaphysically, spiritually,
还是因果层面 宇宙层面 跨时空层面...
karmically, cosmically, inter-dimensionally...
各种层面
Et cetera.
布朗斯基先生想要表达的是 各位面前的这个人
What Mr. Blonsky is trying to say is that the man you see before you
已经不是过去的埃米尔·布朗斯基了
is not the same Emil Blonsky as before.
现在他唯一的愿望 就是能够对社会有所贡献
All he wants now is to be a contributing member of society.
如果得到假释 你有住的地方吗
If released, would you have a place to live?
有 我可以保证
Yeah. You can rely on that.
布朗斯基先生确实拥有一块土地 他打算在那里工作和生活
Mr. Blonsky does own a plot of land on which he plans to work and reside.
他是要去种地吗
He's going into farming?
不 实际上他计划在那里 开设一个冥想训练营
No. Actually, he plans to open a meditation retreat on the property.
这就非常...你懂的...
So, just very... Well, you know...
那布朗斯基先生 做这件事的资金来源呢
And how does Mr. Blonsky intend to fund this endeavor?
布朗斯基先生现在
Mr. Blonsky is currently
和七位笔友建立了长期深厚的感情
in a long-term committed relationship with several pen pals.
她们每一位都承诺 给予他资金上的支持
All of whom have pledged to financially support him.
打断一下 我觉得...
Excuse me. If I could...
-我可以说明一下吗  -不用
- May I clarify? Yeah. - No.
布莱尔 露丝 玛塔 西拉 亚历杭德罗 伊冯娜 还有妮科莱特都是我的笔友
Blair, Ruth, Marta, Sheila, Alejandra, Yvonne and Nicolette are my soulmates.
我们通过监狱的笔友计划相识
We met through the prison pen pal program.
她们让我变得更好
They are my better eighths.
我爱你们
Love you.
我认为这部分不需要继续展开了 还有其它问题吗
I don't think we need to get into that any further. Any other questions?
布朗斯基开办了监狱识字项目
Blonsky started the prison's literacy program.
无数犯人在他的帮助下学会了阅读
He's helped countless prisoners learn how to read.
证人 - 职务
他带领犯人 进行冥想和瑜伽训练
He leads guided meditation and yoga for the prisoners.
-他把我从失败的婚姻中拯救了出来 -没事的 卡尔 哭出来吧
- He saved me from a bad marriage. - That's it, Carl. Let it flow.
图书馆现在已经不是 僻静的杀人场所了
Now the library is more than just a quiet place to shiv someone.
犯人们不做马桶红酒了 都改做马桶康普茶了
Instead of toilet wine, prisoners make toilet kombucha.
-我释怀了 琳达 -我为你骄傲 卡尔
- I release you, Linda. - Proud of you, Carl.
-我真的很爱你 -好了 卡尔说完了
- I love you so much. - Yeah, okay, we're done with Carl.
就这些 布朗斯基先生的越狱行为 还没有解释呢
Is that all? Because there's still the matter of Mr. Blonsky's escape.
这个行为是情有可原的 那个证人会出面解释
Yes, there were extenuating circumstances that the witness will explain.
如果他决定现身的话
If he ever decides to show up.
我很抱歉 沃尔特斯小姐 还有埃米尔
My apologies, Ms. Walters and Emil.
-总算来了 -我没看时间
- Ah! Finally. - I lost track of time.
我今天请王来作证
I've asked Wong here today
因为他应该为 埃米尔·布朗斯基的越狱行为负责
because he is the man responsible for Emil Blonsky leaving prison.
并且我坚信 各位在听完他的陈述之后
And I do think you will see this whole thing in a totally different light
会对本案有完全不同的看法
after hearing from him.
你们听说过“组手”吗
Have you ever heard of a kumite?
我恳请驳回 对我方委托人的全部指控
I'd like to move for dismissal of all charges against my client.
依据是什么
On what grounds?
鲁纳女士是阿斯加德 现在叫新阿斯加德外交官的女儿
Runa is the daughter of an Elfin diplomat on Asgard and now in New Asgard.
-这事你知道吗  -因此她享有外交豁免权
- Did you know about this? - As such, she has diplomatic immunity.
她在新阿斯加德也许有外交豁免权 但是这里不是新阿斯加德
She may have diplomatic immunity in New Asgard, but we are not in New Asgard.
不好意思 法官大人
Excuse me, Your Honor,
但是阿斯加德不是一个地方 而是一个民族 所以...
but Asgard is not a place, it is a people. Therefore, I...
雷神索尔的即兴演讲 是不能被法庭所采纳的
Thor's inspirational speeches are not admissible in court.
法官大人 案情非常清晰明了
Your Honor, this case is very cut and dry.
我的委托人被一个诈骗专家 骗走了17万5000美金
My client was defrauded of $175,000 by a scam artist.
他所遭受的
He deserves compensation
经济损失和情感创伤 理应得到赔偿
for the financial and emotional trauma that he's suffered.
我的委托人与布科夫斯基先生的交往 是基于你情我愿的
My client and Mr. Bukowski were in a consensual relationship
-而且涉及角色扮演 -真恶心
- and engaged in role-play. - Oh, gross.
没有哪个理性的成年人会相信 我的委托人发来的信息
No rational adult would have believed my client's texts
来自梅根·西·斯塔莉安本人
- were from the real Megan Thee Stallion.
布科夫斯基先生 在完全知情的情况下
Mr. Bukowski knew he was dating Miss Runa
与鲁纳小姐约会交往 而现在他想结束这段关系
and went along with it until it no longer suited him.
我不知情
I did not.
这只是一段破裂的感情 并非一场骗局
This was a relationship gone bad, not a scam.
布科夫斯基先生被爱情蒙蔽了双眼
Mr. Bukowski was blinded by love.
他绝对相信和他约会的是 真正的梅根·西·斯塔莉安
He absolutely believed that he was dating the real Megan Thee Stallion.
我必须得说 我很难相信 布科夫斯基先生会如此轻易受骗
I must say, I find it hard to believe that Mr. Bukowski could be fooled so easily.
而你对此有举证责任 普格利泽先生
And the onus is on you to prove that, Mr. Pugliese.
也就是说 我同意本案开庭审理
That being said, I'll allow this to go to trial.
所以 鲁纳小姐 你申请驳回诉讼的请求不予批准
So, Miss Runa, your motion to dismiss is denied.
搞定
Crushed that.
等这个案子结了 我就取消订阅那个“勾搭好莱坞”
And when this is over, I'm canceling my Hollywood Hookups subscription.
他们显然没有审查机制
There's clearly no vetting process.
考虑到刚刚收到的最新信息 我要更改判决
In light of some new information I have just received, I'm changing my ruling.
得了吧 鲁纳 这可太过分了
Come on, Runa. This is getting a little broad.
冒充法官可是违法的 赶紧给我下来
Impersonating a judge is illegal. Get down from there.
这对我们非常有利
This is very good for us.
布朗斯基先生离开监狱 完全是我强迫他的
Yuck. In regard to Mr. Blonsky vacating his cell, I gave him no choice.
但是回到监狱来 绝对是他自己的选择
But it was absolutely his choice to return.
我让他留在卡玛泰姬 现在正是一年中最好的季节
I offered him asylum at the Kamar-Taj, which is lovely this time of the year.
但是他断然拒绝 坚持要回监狱
But he was quite adamant he be returned
他坚持继续服刑 并以此偿还他对社会欠下的债
to serve out his sentence and repay his debt to society.
谢谢你
Thank you.
如您所见 埃米尔·布朗斯基 是被迫离开监狱的 并非出于自愿
So you see, Emil Blonsky was forced out of his cell against his will.
而当他可以立刻重获自由时 却主动选择回到监狱里
And even when offered instant freedom, he chose to return to his cell.
一个罪犯不会做出这样的举动
These are not the actions of a criminal
只有洗心革面 真心改过的人才会如此
but of a reformed man who truly wants to do the right thing.
好吧 就算埃米尔·布朗斯基没做错
Well, that may be true of Emil Blonsky,
但是如果他失控变身成憎恶
but when Blonsky uncontrollably becomes Abomination,
他不就是一头嗜血的狂暴怪物吗
isn't he a raging monster out for blood?
打断一下 我有办法打消您的顾虑...
Uh... Excuse me. If I could just put your minds at ease...
-不行 绝对不行 -稍等一下
- Oh, no, absolutely not. - Hang on a sec.
-不 -怎么了
- No. No, no. - What?
埃米尔 不要这样
Emil. Emil, no.
-别担心 珍妮佛 -不要 求你了
- It's fine, Jen. - No, please.
不 你...不能...不
No, no, no, no. You... Don't... No, no, no, no.
天啊
Oh, my God.
不
- No, no, no, no.
大家不要害怕
Everybody just relax
快跑 把他...
- Get out of there! Get him...
-天啊 -停
- Oh, my God! - Stop, stop, stop, stop.
-天啊 -等等 没必要动用武力
- Oh, my God. - Hang on. Force is not necessary.
各位看到了 我完全可以控制自己
As you can see, I'm in full control.
够了 赶快变回来
That's enough! Change back now!
快变回来 他没事的 他完全没问题
Get down! Down. He's fine. It's fine. He's totally fine.
-埃米尔 -好吧 冷静一下
- Emil! - All right, all right. Calm down.
拜托...
Please...
女士们 先生们 恳请各位原谅布朗斯基先生的热情
Ladies and gentlemen, I beg you to forgive Mr. Blonsky's enthusiasm.
他并不是想要吓到大家
He didn't intend to frighten anyone.
实际上 这恰好证明了 无论何时何地
In fact, this proves that in every instance,
布朗斯基先生本来都能摆脱监禁 但是却选择留在牢房里
Mr. Blonsky could have broken free but has chosen to remain in his cell.
而且他出色的服刑记录表明 在全部监禁时间里
As his stellar prison record reflects, Mr. Blonsky spent his entire incarceration
布朗斯基先生严格训练 高度自律
practicing a strict regimen of training and self-discipline
这样在他重新回到社会的时候
so that he may walk among his fellow citizens
就不会再变成那个暴虐的憎恶了
with no chance of becoming a rampaging Abomination again.
他应该得到自由的权利 成为普通公民 为社会作出贡献
He deserves a future as a free man and a productive citizen.
谢谢你 沃尔特斯小姐
Thank you, Ms. Walters.
今天先休庭 我们会评估所有的情况
We will adjourn for today and consider all of the facts.
得出结论后 再宣布复庭
We will reconvene once a decision has been reached.
请给这位先生找件衣服
And please, let's get this man some clothes.
-好 -至于这位王先生
- Oh, yeah. - And as for Mr. Wong...
叫王就行 至上尊者 秘术法师
Just "Wong." The Sorcerer Supreme. Master of the Mystic Arts.
卡玛泰姬的领袖及前图书管理员
Leader and former librarian of Kamar-Taj.
行了 你应该意识到
Yeah. You realize that
你刚刚承认了协助罪犯越狱 这构成了犯罪
you've just admitted to facilitating a prisoner escape, which is a crime.
我得撤了
I must depart.
她出来了
There she is.
如果布朗斯基再搞破坏 你准备怎么对付他
How do you plan to take Blonsky down when he rampages again?
有人说你也是布朗斯基的笔友之一 你有何回应
What about claims that you're one of Blonsky's rumored soulmates?
还有传言说你获得超能力
Is there any truth to the rumors you got your powers
-是因为黑帮谋杀阴差阳错 -什么
- from a Mafia hit gone wrong? - What?
珍妮佛·沃尔特斯匆匆而过 她无疑是想避开
That was Jennifer Walters rushing by, undoubtedly hoping to avoid the protesters
聚集在监狱大门外的抗议者们
that are gathered just outside the gates here.
然后我发现有个示威者在我车上写了
And then I get to my car, and some protester has written on it,
“怪物替怪物辩护”
"Monster defending a monster."
只要接受个小采访 就没有这些烦恼了
This can go away with one little interview.
-“早安加州”一直想请你呢 -不用了 谢谢 我肯定不去
- Good Day LA is thirsty for you. - No, thank you. Hard pass.
真希望这个案子早点了结
- I cannot wait for this to be over
这样我就能继续做个 平凡的无名律师了
so I can go back to being a normal anonymous lawyer.
-只不过碰巧能变成浩克 -你在说什么啊
- Who also happens to be a Hulk. - What are you talking about?
珍妮佛 现在木已成舟了 你现在可是话题人物
Jen, the genie is out of the bottle, girl. You are a story now.
好吧 不 我一点都不想这样
Okay, yeah. No. I don't want this.
天啊 你竟然怀了憎恶的宝宝
Oh, my God. You're pregnant with the Abomination's baby,
还在炫耀你的小肚子
and you're flaunting a baby-bump.
-这就是孩子他爸  -是啊
- That's who the father is? - Yeah.
真要命 丹尼斯·布科夫斯基
Good God. Dennis Bukowski.
-不 你需要喝一杯 -两条故事线终于有交集了 不错
- Yeah. No, you're gonna need that. - Connecting the A and B story. Nice.
你们俩怎么能和他共事那么久的
How did you two work with him for so long?
我在脑海里早就用各种方式 杀了他好多次了
Oh, I killed him in my head several times, in many different ways.
但是他却一直认为 妮基对他有意思
And yet he was convinced that she had a crush on him.
-这家伙的妄想症已经无药可治了 -我觉得他就是恶心
- The man is almost terminally deluded. - I'd call him gross.
对 就是恶心
Yeah. Just gross.
你愿意在宣誓之后再说一遍吗
Hey, would you be willing to say that under oath?
本人在此郑重宣誓
I swear the testimony I'm about to give today
本人所说完全属实 绝无虚言
is the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth.
巴戈 为什么珍妮佛是最佳人选  我给了你那么多我的哥们
Hey, P-Dog, how is Jen our best option? I gave you a whole list of my boys.
珍妮佛能帮我们拿下这案子 相信我
Jen is gonna help us clinch this. Trust me.
沃尔特斯小姐 你如何描述 你和布科夫斯基先生的关系
Ms. Walters, how would you describe your relationship to Mr. Bukowski?
我们在地方检察院共事过几年时间
We worked together for several years at the DA's office.
也就是说你非常了解 布科夫斯基先生吗
Would you say that you know Mr. Bukowski fairly well?
当然 我们经常会一起处理案子
Definitely. We worked regularly on cases together,
所以我确实与布科夫斯基先生 相处过很长时间
so I've spent a lot of time with Mr. Bukowski.
他会和你谈及他的个人生活吗  特别是感情生活
Did he ever share his personal life with you? Specifically, his dating life.
是的 他会提到 而且是经常主动提到
Yes, he would, prolifically and unprompted.
那是因为你八卦
You wanted to know.
你会如何描述布科夫斯基先生 在感情生活中的状态呢
How would you characterize Mr. Bukowski in relation to his romantic life?
自我陶醉 盲目自信 自命不凡
Self-absorbed, chauvinistic, conceited.
他曾经说到 自己在纽约是满分 在洛杉矶则是爆表
He once described himself as a New York 10 and an LA 11.
他把自己的办公室命名为丹尼斯星球...
He nicknamed his office the Dennisphere...
反对 这与本案无关
Objection. Relevance.
布科夫斯基先生 你知道自己不是代理律师吗
Mr. Bukowski, need I remind you that you're not representing yourself here?
而且这是你方证人
And this is your witness.
但是我认可你的观点 普格利泽先生 请回到正题
But I agree. Mr. Pugliese, get to your point.
在这个法庭上我已多次提到
It's been stated many times in this courtroom
一个具有正常理智的人
that a man of reasonable intelligence
不可能认为自己交往的对象 是梅根·西·斯塔莉安本人的
would never think that he was dating the real Megan Thee Stallion.
在你看来 沃尔特斯小姐 你认为丹尼斯·布科夫斯基
In your opinion, Ms. Walters, do you think that Dennis Bukowski would believe
会认为他的个人魅力 足以折服梅根·西·斯塔莉安吗
that he could actually pull Megan Thee Stallion?
是的 从病理学角度讲 丹尼斯·布科夫斯基不是个正常人
Yes. Dennis Bukowski is an almost pathologically entitled man.
他绝对会认为他就是在和 梅根·西·斯塔莉安本人约会
He would absolutely believe that he's dating the real Megan Thee Stallion
因为他是一个妄想症患者
because he is truly that delusional.
没有其它问题了 法官大人
No further questions, Your Honor.
关于布科夫斯基诉鲁纳一案 我在此宣判丹尼斯·布科夫斯基
In the case of Bukowski v. Runa, I award full damages to Dennis Bukowski
获得全部损失赔偿金 共计17万5000美元
in the amount of $175,000.
除此以外
In addition,
我们对本案的被告冒充法官的行为 判处60天监禁
we also sentence the defendant to 60 days for impersonating a judge.
不
No, no, no, no, no, no.
判得好 梅根·西·斯塔莉安 是独一无二的
That's right. There's only one Megan Thee Stallion.
大家嗨起来
Make some noise.
你们觉得我有机会 和真的梅根交往吗
You guys think I have a shot with the real Megan Thee Stallion?
我该回去找她吗
Should I go back?
别了 拜托 千万别去 谢谢你刚才的证词 珍妮佛
No. No. Please, don't do that. Thanks for that testimony in there, Jen.
乐意效劳
It was my pleasure.
令人不爽的是 那个精灵只受了点小惩罚
The sad part is that elf's just gonna get a slap on the wrist.
真希望可以移除她的超能力
I wish there was a way we could remove her powers
这样以后就不会再有人受害了
and make sure she doesn't victimize anyone else.
丹尼斯这个主意不错啊
Oh! Did Dennis Bukowski just give me an idea?
这件事可要保密
That will stay between us.
我们刚刚收到消息 假释委员会已经做出决定了
We've just received word the parole board has reached a decision.
经过审查他的记录
After reviewing his record,
我们在此批准布朗斯基先生的假释申请 立即生效
we hereby grant Mr. Blonsky's release on parole, effective immediately.
太好了
Yes.
作为获得假释的条件
- As a condition of his parole,
布朗斯基先生将被永远禁止 变身成憎恶
Mr. Blonsky is prohibited from turning into Abomination indefinitely,
并且被要求永远佩戴抑制器
and is ordered to wear an inhibitor in perpetuity.
上述要求如有任何违背 他会立即被再次收监入狱
Any violation of this condition will result in his immediate return to prison.
明白 谢谢
Understood. Thank you.
谢谢你 珍妮佛 我欠你一个人情
Thank you, Jen. I'm in your debt, you know.
当然仅限精神层面
Spiritually, of course.
平时低调点 我就这点要求
Just stay out of the news. That's all I ask.
我可不想再看到 任何有关你我的故事了
I don't wanna read any more stories about either of us.
这恐怕有点难
You might wanna reconsider that.
无论如何他们都会给你编个故事的
They're gonna write a story about you one way or the other, you know.
其实还不如你自己来讲
Better to be a part of it, really.
市民新闻 晚间报道
憎恶现在已经重获自由了
The Abomination is now a free man.
今天来到演播室的 是帮助他获得自由的律师 女浩克
Here with us in the studio, the lawyer responsible for his release, She-Hulk.
我的名字叫珍妮佛·沃尔特斯 不叫女浩克
Yeah, my name is Jennifer Walters, not She-Hulk,
而且我的委托人叫埃米尔·布朗斯基 不叫憎恶
and my client's name is Emil Blonsky, not the Abomination.
明白
Got it.
由于这个案件的高关注度 以及你本人是个浩克的缘故
The high-profile nature of this case and the fact that you yourself are a Hulk
让你突然成为公众瞩目的焦点
has catapulted you into the public eye.
那么给我们讲讲 你是怎么想到女浩克这个名字的
So, tell us, how did you come up with the name She-Hulk?
说来有趣 这个名字不是我起的
Oh! Funny story, I didn't.
不知道是谁在新闻里提到的
Some random guy on the news came up with it
可能他自己都没多想 然后就流传开了
after thinking about it for, like, two seconds, but it stuck.
现在不管我喜不喜欢 我就永远变成女浩克了
So, now whether I like it or not, I am forever She-Hulk.
好的 我们休息片刻
Great. We have to take a break.
随后女浩克将分享 她的饮食和健身小秘密
When we come back, She-Hulk shares her diet and exercise secrets.
不好意思 分享什么
I'm sorry. What?
抓住她了 快上啊 兄弟们 我抓住她了
- I got her. Come on, guys. I got her.
等等
Oh, wait.
放开我
Get off me.
如果你要明目张胆地 炫耀自己的超能力
If you're gonna strut around showing off your powers,
你最好有真本事
you better be able to back it up.
我什么时候明目张胆地 炫耀我自己的超能力了
When did I ever strut around and show off my powers?
你们是打劫了 阿斯加德的建筑工人吗
Did you guys rob an Asgardian construction worker?
是啊
Yeah.
好吧 动手吧
All right, let's do this.
对不起
Sorry.
好吧 我错了
Okay, bad idea, bad idea.
-撤退 -快走
- Fall back! - Go, go, go!
好吧 伙计们 我承认和预期的差别有点大
Okay, fellas, I admit that did not go exactly as I imagined it.
雷球 你觉得呢
Thunderball, did you get it?
是啊 一旦她变成女浩克 那丑陋的绿皮肤就刀枪不入了
No. Once she turned into She-Hulk, I couldn't pierce that nasty green skin.
该死 老板一定会暴怒的
Damn it. Boss is gonna be mad.
《律师女浩克》
你好 这不是我最喜欢的委托人嘛
Hi. There's my new favorite client.
这里需要你的签名
Just... Just your signature there.
这里签首字母就行 好的
And then just initial. Good.
还有上面这里
And initials up here.
你可比我上一个律师有意思多了
Oh, you are way more fun than my last lawyer.
-我会为你全力以赴的 梅根·西·斯塔莉安 -放松点
- I will kill for you, Megan Thee Stallion. - Dial it back.
字幕翻译: 虫二